eadulthost.com 2014-07-04

# Privacy Policy | eAdultHost

    PRIVACY POLICY
    This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use personal and other specific information that is obtained in connection with your access to the services (individually and collectively the “Services”) provided by eadulthost.com.
    If you do not agree with any terms of this Privacy Policy or the applicable Terms of Service, please do not use the Services. By accessing any part of the Services, you agree to be bound by and have accepted this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service in full. If you have any queries relating to this Privacy Policy, please contact us. 
    
    Scope
    This Privacy Policy concerns the collection and use of personal and other specific information that is collected through your access to the Services. We are committed to protecting the privacy of Users, and accordingly, we do not collect personally identifying information unless it is provided to us voluntarily and knowingly, and do not share any information with anyone outside of our Company other than described herein. You are under no obligation to provide us with any requested information, but without it we may not be able to take the action requested.
    
    Minors
    If you are under 18 years old, you may not use the Services or provide any of your personal information including, but not limited to, your name, address and email address.
    
    Information Collection and Use
    We collect personally identifying information to give you access to the Services, to optimize your experience using the Services, to respond to a request, and, if applicable, for email communications. For such use, you may be required to provide your e-mail address and other personally-identifying information (such as your name, phone number or date of birth) as we may deem necessary. When you provide any personally identifying information, you acknowledge that you are knowingly and voluntarily providing us the information, and that all provided information is accurate and up-to-date. 
    We may use your IP address and other related information such as browser type, time zone settings, and operating system in order to grant you access to and otherwise administer Services. 
    We collect certain usage information about our Services, such as the number and frequency of Users and/or Users' Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, which are automatically logged by our servers and are used by us and our partners to analyse user activity at an aggregate level, such as the number of visits and geographic optimization. This data is used only in the aggregate and does not include any personally identifying information. 
    
    Your Access to and Control over Information
    You may opt out of any future communications from us at any time. At your request you can request the information we have about you; change or correct any information; or delete any information we have about you.
    
    Information Sharing
    We do not sell, rent or pass on your personally-identifiable information to any third party other than as necessary to provide the Services unless we have your consent or as otherwise set forth herein. All third parties that require such information to provide the Services will agree to use any such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy. 
    We may provide such information to third parties without your consent if we reasonably believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations; (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or our safety or the safety of our users or the public as required or permitted by law. 
    
    Provider may use a third party to deal with advertisements on the Services. Our advertising partners will serve ads that it believes are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information related to your use of the Services. This information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, email address or telephone number. In order to do this, we or our advertising partner may need to place a cookie on your computer or device.
    
    Data Security
    We use a variety of security measures including encryption and authentication to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control. Registered accounts are secured by your created username and password, and we take precautions to insure that account information is kept private. You are solely responsible for the security of your username and password.
    We use reasonable measures to protect information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to information to those who need access to perform their job functions, such as our technical staff, and they are instructed that the information is to be used only in adherence with the provisions set forth in this Privacy Policy and applicable laws. 
    Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of information. 
    We use encryption and authentication tools among other methods to protect your personal information. E-mails you send us are not necessarily secure when they are transmitted. If your communication is sensitive or includes highly confidential information, you may want to provide it by post. 
    
    Cookies and Web Beacons
    Like many companies, we use "cookie" and/or "web beacon" technology. Cookies may give us such information as your log in details and when you have accessed the Services before. Web Beacons are tags that can monitor the behavior of a user accessing the Services.
    Cookies are used during your connection with the Services to allow you free access to the Services and to use the Services without repeatedly requiring you to re-enter your user name and password. The cookies do not provide us with any way to contact you. When you log off or leave the Services, the cookies file is automatically removed.
    You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you may have to enable cookies from in order to use and access some of the Services.
    Information recorded through web beacons is used to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users. 
    
    Other Information Provided
    If you provide us with information other than personally-identifying information, including suggestions about the Services, all such information shall be solely owed by us and may be used, reproduced, modified, distributed and disclosed by us in any manner in our sole discretion, without compensation to you. 
    
    Changes in Privacy Policy
    We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revised terms. It is your responsibility to check periodically for any changes we may make to the Privacy Policy and your continuing to access the Services indicates your acceptance of any current Privacy Policy.
    
    Miscellaneous
    This Privacy Policy constitutes the entire agreement between you and us with respect to the privacy policy related to the Services. 
    This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Bulgaria applicable therein, without regard to conflict of laws. You irrevocably consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located Varna in connection with any action arising out of or related to this Privacy Policy. You waive any objection based on lack of personal jurisdiction, place of residence, improper venue or forum non-convenience in any such action.
    If any court having competent jurisdiction holds any provision of this Privacy Policy invalid or unenforceable in any respect, such provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permitted by law, and the remaining provisions of this Privacy Policy shall continue in full force and effect. 
    No waiver of any provision of this Privacy Policy shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such provision or any other provision of this Privacy Policy.
    
    How to Contact Us
    If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us 
    By e-mail to support@eadulthost.com
    By visiting the Contact Us section; or
    By post: Daniel Simeonov, Mladost, Bl.150, Vh.3, Ap.9, Varna 9020, BULGARIA
